Right, watch the secrets unfold, there's magic in her hands, it's for what the future holds.
Now PM lights up, mics, hot chaos in the street, we need a call, I'm in for a word.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, so, let the tarot move with the rhythm.
every card an open door feel the romance in every arcane war destiny entwined as the moon begins to
Pigeons in her gaze Time can steal this moment
Life's uncertain dance We chase with love woven
Pulled and danced to the mystery
Facebook. Okay. Okay. Nobody can't nobody see you right now.
Just the screens up. We just need to make sure that you know who the hell I'm talking
to. I'll let you see here. There you can be talking to me.
Okay. Okay. Cool. Thank you so much, lady. Yeah, there you go. Yeah.
So I've been, I've been on 200 shows in the past 90 days.
Do you make in the rounds on the YouTube?
But I am I'm unknown famous, but I am everybody knows beyond the stream yard shows and stuff like that
What are you from I can hear a little bit of a southern accent. I'm from Kentucky. I'm from South Carolina. Oh
Right someone in South Carolina fuck around and find out also
probably. Yeah, I learned about that. What faithful means if they have room.
Look around and find out if you want to, baby. That's for the style. Yeah.
Hey, can you see how I look? See how I look, right?
Hey, Psyche, can you put a link in there?
I like a hot mess right now. I just got to work, but there you go.
I see what the main owner of the show, he does tarot cards and stuff like that. And I like to
respect other tarot card readers and stuff like that to do that thing and stuff like that. Everybody
have different techniques to read people and stuff like that. Well, that's pretty dope.
Now he's between Meezer, as Meezer has a shirt off too.
Oh, Meezer's here?
Yeah.
Well, let me ask the host this.
Host, do you do remote viewing?
Do you ever try remote viewing?
Remote viewing?
Um, you know, it's like, you know, I like to, um, I like to, uh, you know, do astral
projection in a, in a certain way, and I did the dream world, but, you know, remote viewing,
you know, I think, uh,
You didn't get astral viewing?
The places I've been in the astral realm. Well, I think I think even like I'd be in the imagination in a way is the astral realm
Also, you know, the dream world is the astral realm. I think that who's the dream in yeah
Yeah, I'm talking about the real deal the real deal. Yeah, thanks. Well, I know it's like, you know
There's there's people that have like I have that really strong strong sight
No, that like they can close their eyes and instantly
You know, Alistair Crowley went through a lot of the you know, he would did the Anokian
Yeah, Jack Parsons JPL and stuff so but Alistair Crowley talked a lot about how you know, he like he has these
I forgot what his book is called, but there's these 30 Anokian ethers, and each one is a different place and things like that.
And you can verify, people have seen similar, almost exact similar things in the place and stuff like that.
And so it's interesting if you start to do those invocations and things like that, you can do and then you basically close your eyes.
But he said it was a lot of like imagination involvement too, like using your, your inner sight.
Hey, throw a link overnight. I gotta switch. I gotta switch devices. Okay. Well, we also like
We like you know every every like every invention we have every like everything with it was first
First in the mind, and so that's like a lot about the magician card is when they go as above so below is like it's like taking these
Making these these visions these thoughts and manifesting them and bringing them to the world
And so it's like but everything starts in the mind, you know, and so I teach manifesting to like how to manifest
A lot of people take it because it
It they make you like it's hard. It's not hard at all
Once you get the ability that you ever heard a gateway experience. Yeah, it's like, you know, it's like a certain
Yeah, my room in row and that's like, you know, he's certain. It's like the hemi sink and stuff like that or
Releasing your mind of doubt
The trick is to release the doubt from your mind, which is crazy because like we're always all programmed to doubt everything
Right, we're supposed to question everything. I mean, it's it's how we it's like it's
They train they trained for ego minds though a miser
With the first ball keep your down and stuff because no ego mind don't give a damn what it is what you say
Yeah, you're right. I hear what you're talking about the ego. You're talking about the ego in your mind doubting
You're totally right. I'm good page
Yeah, Miser I really appreciate it that convo the other night. I don't know if you remember this is school speaking but
Yeah, that was really cool, man. That was
The worst thing in the world is when you go and you order a fast food meal and you get home
And you're like yay, and they eat it and you go to take a drink of your soda, and there's no fucking song
I don't like
So what's the show about? It's like y'all just sit back and like we just hang out and stuff talk shit and all that
I'm gonna play me a story that talks shit. Yeah chicken chicken right now chicken patties in my air fryer
Yeah, I just threw them in I threw two of them in for
degrees 13 minutes and then the sesame seed hamburger buns a little mayo
Romaine lettuce one leaf and some provolone cheese the melt
Yeah, you're talking to Tyson
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, I got
Well, I'm drinking tonight when you fucked up you
There you go, buddy I got that one and then this one too I got those two
the green one. These are lightly breaded chicken strips and then these are the patties and you know
it's nice I put it in the air fryer and then my phone connects to the air fryer it's got the
bluetooth on the app and then it tells you like it tells you the the chicken is you know rare
Okay, yeah, like it tells you exactly like where it's at like
Yeah, I thought it was pretty cool
But meserman, I learned a lot from you the other day. That was that was pretty cool, man
Yeah, that was that was that was a good conversation. Uh, you were pretty sure that red is a little red book
Yes, I got it, I got it from the library, the library that's online, the e-library.
So I got it on that, so I have it in my phone now, I can read it, and then you also were
very patient with me.
Psyche, he was teaching me about tarot cards, because I knew nothing.
And I always feel bad asking you questions when there's 10 people online, and I have
no clue.
Let me tell you a one-seeker, let me tell you, but I'm gonna cut you off.
One-seeker by the tarot cards is you can't be biased with the cards.
The cards don't lie, and the cards will know your energy and they respect.
You have to respect the cards.
I know people, I had to get on them that they're biased about politics.
They're trying to use cards for politics because they hate Trump or whoever.
Hey, you can't use the cards for that.
It's not going to work.
The cars are non-biased cars the cars the cars don't live it sometimes people can't and so it's like, you know
It's like a better
Most people that do read it's like so many tarot cards came out of nowhere everybody doing tarot cards now everybody got a job
Like hold on that everybody can't do this shit
Okay, it's because everybody's using it for like as it is a trend for monetary gain and taking people like advantage of people
Making a mockery of what we actually do
I didn't have to use social media, I don't need social media for validation and stuff
like that and put it out there because I've been doing this for over 15 years.
Well, I like what Miser said about how each card can affect somebody differently each
I like every card. Every card can be interpreted to anyone's potential situation. You know,
they're not meant to tell you something you don't already know. It's something that hits
you intuitively, based on what the card is. I could pull out any card, any one card from the deck.
and it'll apply to every person here in the chat.
Yeah, that's what you said.
Because remember what I told you?
I was like, I still haven't gotten a reading yet, not once.
And Syke was doing a reading the other day.
And then I keep forgetting that other guy, Syke,
that you did the reading with the other day.
But he asked me, do I want a reading?
And I was like, no, no, I don't want one.
And then he's like, oh, well, Tarot's not for everyone.
I'm like, that's not what it's about.
It's about if somebody says something to me,
and I say, no, let's, no.
And then they say, oh, you're lying.
You know, well, let me listen to the host, listen to the host
question, what doesn't for someone else, right?
See, like me, when I do my technique of reading cards, like I
could spray, I could spray, I got different techniques. I
could spray the cards out and run my hand across it. And my
hand would start getting warm to the car for that person. I
don't know if that works.
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
and you put your hand over them cars and that warm sensation
come on your hand over that car and you pick that car
and that car is all about that person right there
and it goes into a whole another...
What I found for me what you know, everyone has a different technique style to have different things that work for them. There's
But what happens for me is that all like certain details will pop out when I'm doing personal reading like certain details that I've even
I've been noticed and like then they'll turn out to have relevance to that person like the certain the certain detail like I
the chariot for someone before the chariot has these black and white sphinxes on it
and as usually I'll say oh the chariot's moving forward but it's like I talked to somebody and I
was like I saw this a black and white popped out at me I'm like did you get arrested recently
because it seems like there's something with them at the police or there yeah and then they were like
There's so many examples of that happening, right?
So let me ask you this, host, what kind of,
what certain spreads do you use to help this spread
or like, want three-car spread?
Yeah, I like to do, I mean, I do different types of readings.
Like, you know, I was doing like three free three-car readings,
you know, you can say past, present, past, present,
or in the future and stuff like that.
Not like I always say, I don't predict the future.
It's like, and the future's always up to us, but it's saying.
Yeah, I eat that all the time.
Yeah, and so also sometimes I'll do more cards and I'll feel like, oh, a couple more
needed for clarification and things like that.
I also can do a full Celtic cross spread and everything, and it's, you know, that can
show a lot of detailed things and things in different situations and stuff like that.
And so.
but yeah there's lots of ways and also you know also as the page said about monetary gain
i mean there's there are certainly scam artists that you know that will
that they don't even believe in their own ability but they're you know but they just for money
but i think it's okay to charge for readings like because it is like especially if there's
Also people sometimes when they get something for free, they don't really appreciate it
But when they pay for something they'll they will appreciate it or then they'll take it more and take it more seriously
Yeah, so
Okay, I'm sorry here you go. No, it's all good
It's like what you do like you doing really like it's like cuz I had one client
Sometimes I don't even have to use the cards.
They just come to me.
Visions in my head and this person,
this person was a suicidal person, this female.
So I was talking to her and trying to get her right
and stuff like, and one thing people don't understand
about doing psychic readings and stuff like that,
after I was trying to help her out
with her energy healing with her suicidal thoughts.
I took her to us out thousand and came to me and I wanted I wanted to kill myself.
Yeah, okay, careful with some of the language use you have to say like I'm
alive being and stuff like that. I just I just don't want to lie myself.
I'm taking her energy and I had to learn that. See I was a rookie back in that time. I was like
almost 15 years ago. I was doing with shamans and all that and I took her energy when I was
starting out and I had them thoughts in my head for over two weeks and I had to get rid of them.
Of her thought that I is a word from her. Mm-hmm. Yeah, cuz we yeah
We do we can't take on other people's energy and things like that when we do it
That's also why you know, it's like, you know, it's sometimes charging is not the worst thing
It's because there is other energy we're taking on and stuff like that and it can be draining to us
It can yeah, I can't put us in a bad state of mind if they're in a bad state of mind
Okay, yeah, me there's three of swords. That's a heart like a heartbreak card, right? It's like
But it's also, I believe, I believe, I also, it can be, I mean, you're ready to heal, but you need to take those swords out of the heart, usually, to be able to heal, right?
You need to take away the source of temperance, you know, it's maintaining balance, moderation also is an earth angel, sedentary energy.
One foot in the earth, one foot in the spear.
Can you put in on the big, like, make his big and small on the side?
Yeah, one second.
I was trying to see yeah like that. Yeah, perfect. Sorry. Thank you. This is good
Yeah, that's also feeling like like like you was saying, you know, we've got the three of sorts from before
He's talking about that on the live and stuff, you know, that's kind of heartbreaking shit, you know, so
So that popped out is that as you guys were talking, you know, the three of swords and then psyche goes to explain with the three of swords
It's like the heartbreak and everything but uh, you know, everyone heals from that, you know
So that's that's right there at the healing, you know, that's balancing out, you know your emotions
You know
Yeah, let me ask you I don't even know anything about it. So I I'm just learning since I came to psyches channel
I deal with extra-trustful beings and all that to deal with all that too. You won't say double mission
But yeah, we do that you can you can summon them and all that
It's technique, but we don't get on all all that. I try to talk to you product about that
But yeah, like Dean would be see what I'm going to ask your world. I'm always surrounded by the military
Okay, yeah, I'm sure there are many people hired if I'm a lot of people they're talented and they they they will
Use those talents, you know the military is in the astral world. They walk around they do their operations and stuff like that
In the ass around a lot of people don't know that CIA. They're all in the astral world
They're in the astral realms every day. They do this stuff
And I don't believe that I know I know there's been they have a lot of secret projects like we have no
But if I move there's five of wands
It's like, you know, I think it's up to a healthy competition
I usually say because they're like kind of fighting with like sticks and stuff like that like you know playing a game and stuff like
This three suits you taught me what's that last one that you said sometimes has different names
Wands it's like called something
What's it torture torture tortures it can be like, you know one wand is fire as far as a fire element
About the cars
Mm-hmm. Oh, yeah. The cars would choose you. Is this your first time? The cars would choose you. Let the cars choose for you.
Don't don't get in your mind about oh, I don't think it's the right car. This thing's the right car.
You keep moving your mind. Don't do that. What's when you when you see that car and it's your first impression pull that car?
Don't hold back and don't
I don't think it might not be this low because every time I do that hand thing take me with
the hand and that hand gets vibrate and you start warming up, that's the car and my techniques
are different than other people take me.
You have a lot of different decks, sir, the ones that I just use the regular arm right
away deck.
I like the artwork.
I don't know.
I don't use different decks.
But you see, the decks don't matter.
Well I'm just trying to say what I like like I'm into the art that has to do with famous painters
and like it had like a story about the painters it was really bringing a cool page you know that
deck that you showed me. I hate reading them.
Well, but it's another thing to host. Can you explain to like if you're a beginner
You need to know the history of the cars to the cars love for you to know the history
Who Pamela Coleman Smith is and how it all started in the door order a golden dawn?
And once you know the history of the car the cars will come to you even more quicker
It was it really started as a playing card game in Italy called taro chi and
The Venetian
In the decks and things like that. I'm sorry. If you want if you want to say
I'm just saying, you know, let me ask I got you know Pamela Coleman Smith's
Yeah, I think I think the Golden Dawn
I don't care if I re-stream, do you?
Yeah, go ahead.
Yeah, I was, you know me, I always say.
One of the guys that started bringing it
to the Western, as far as bringing it
to like Western influence was a Mason.
You were Aleister Crowley talking about?
Two ones that like arrived are pretty much.
The first one wasn't Alistair Crowley, it was someone that was before Alistair Crowley.
It might have been after, it might have been after, but they were freemasons.
Yeah, I think you're talking about Mathers, you're talking about McGregor Mathers, or also this guy, his name is Paul something like that.
Yeah, but Pamela will Pamela wasn't in on she wasn't like all plays and stuff
And she was making up little doll figures and stuff like that. She she was the one that
Cohen
LEM and Coleman Coleman
And also, um, also, uh, you know, Alistair Crowley or Alistair Crowley commissioned what he did commissioned
He, um, so he commissioned the art like Lady Frida Harris did the art
Yeah, he was in the order of the going down and he kicked him out right
Well, right he uh
Thank you. I think he took it was kind of a hostile takeover of any source. So he started the OTO and stuff like that
Initiated in Mexico
So they don't necessarily like to claim him there. Let me see
Oh, she died in Cornwall, she lived in Cornwall
There's a deep card right there
He got from the Golden Dawn
You know
Well, right. Well, he really made a public yes, but it's like, I mean, yeah, no, he basically took the information, right? Yeah
He wrote Wicca and stuff like that. He wrote the Wicca books
Well, you were the card I would say that you took too many vaccines
That's funny seven of swords
Oh hell yes
I'm trying to look for find this guy. It's just cool stuff y'all.
One thing y'all have to understand is that the military, the military perfected all this stuff.
Yo, this guy, the guy who made the Rider Waite Tarots, like she illustrated it?
She illustrated it?
He's from Brooklyn.
Arthur, this guy, Arthur, Edward Waite.
Arthur Waite, yeah.
So he's from Brooklyn.
Okay, so the guys look up Paul Foster case as well
He was a Freemason too. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, and he wrote a lot about he wrote about a lot about
Like he put it with the cards a certain way and it's like and then and like different rows and things like that
So is that when you say reverse? Sometimes I hate you say reverse
Is that was reversal? Well, no, I mean, it's like you can they're they're numbered, right?
And then it's like and there's there's a 20 just 20 you and so like the pools like I think the pools
Let me see what what does that mean when you say reverse it came out reversed. Why do you like so?
You alright
What's everybody? What's up everybody over and talk your ish. We're over here hanging with
Reverse cause me and it's a negative polarity. Well, it's a good thing
But sometimes there's negative cards and so it can give it a pause
But psyche was doing a really good
And the guy was like, no, no, that doesn't work.
And he's like, but it came out reverse.
And you said something different to him
because it came out reversed.
And the guy was like, oh, shit,
I didn't think of it that way, you know?
So like, couldn't understand until you said
like the word reverse.
And then he like-
Yeah, it's good to have your cars reverse too
in your day, man.
When you shuffle your day, when you shuffle your day,
man, yeah, reverse cars come out, that's okay.
Yeah, that's part of it.
I'm part of it.
Because they can have the, like the, they had the devil reverse or like, you know, that
can mean like, you know, coming out of an addiction and things like that would work.
That's what you said to him the other day about the addiction and then he was like, oh
shit.
I was with my homeboy the other day and he had the devil car come out and it came with
him manipulation and lies and manipulation.
What's that car?
What is the devil car?
What does it look like?
What is this?
Like what's the number?
Two little people, it's two people standing by and you got chains on them.
And what does it say?
Like the tenets and like what's the devil saying?
Well, the devil says, you know, the devil can be an attachment to the material world because they're in chains, but they're also around there
Yeah, bondage
But also it's interesting around their necks like the chains are loose and so it's like a voluntary bondage and so it's like
Because we can
Pack it up buddy back it up so you can see it. That's the devil corn
No, that's the that's the six of a pinnacle. That's a charity. It's a charity card
But look he's giving to one person and like not the other he can be any of those lever scale
It's like the balance and so he has he's generous, but you know
Right, thank you people dig down deck is different. My deck is a lot
But I don't want to show the the nudity because there's some you don't I'm being careful with that
Was it down the bottom just a devil or what does it say the devil fucking cool looking?
And he has cat ears. You'll notice he has cat ears. He also has breasts. He has he kind of looks like MC
Nemesis body a little bit. No, he has bat wings. He has the rams horns. He's got
Hedgeogram on there and he's got the legs. He's got the animal legs and they're like scary
Yeah, and they're chained but they're chained to her. I can't show her breasts
They're changing
That's fucking scary
Is that the same one you got there?
Why is it scary?
It doesn't mean scary things.
Because I'll tell you, bitch, horror movies don't scare me
like regular traditional slasher comedy.
But like, if you've ever seen the movie The Witch by Robert Eggers,
that's how the devil looks.
The real thing that scares you, the stuff that's...
Yeah.
The devil looks like me and you, baby.
The devil don't look like red hair, red suit with red horns.
Yeah, he looks like that.
You're right.
You're right, son.
But also, also, you know, the devil also is like, you know, everything corresponds to astrology, too
So the devil is like associated with Capricorn, right? And Capricorn is like, you know, can and
And I'm a Capricorn
Are you really?
I'm a Capricorn
Can you guys hear me?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Oh, OK.
I was just kidding.
Never done my talk.
I feel like I've not.
No, I'm listening.
I'm sorry.
I'm listening.
Yeah, you said you're a capricorn.
No, no, sit down.
You're a capricorn.
What?
Capricorn, right, hun?
Hoes, hoes, that's all the hoes.
I was going to say, I'm a Capricorn in Aquarius Clips.
I got to point it out.
But there we go again.
Every time I speak, guys, I'm just saying you know.
Guys, I'm sorry Summers, I'm sorry Summers.
I'm missing hoes, hoes.
I got to point it out.
I think talk can be a part of the conversation, too.
But every time I join it, I get talked over.
okay sorry summer i'm sorry there's a lot of people at it like i know i'm not being a good good
moderator i'm sorry i got to push statement after her okay let's let summer have the floor
please i'd like to i'd like to hear what you have to say okay so okay go ahead that's kind of
no you're you're you're you're you said you say capricorn is Aquarius the cusp and stuff like
And they're also in all in the first house.
And so I have very strong placements there.
And so the cap for foreign queries, good.
I like what you said.
That's pretty much what I think.
Well, one thing I can tell you, I can tell you,
I can tell you, I can tell you, I can tell you,
I can tell you, I can tell you,
Okay, good
Speak
Sorry
Every time I do I get talked over. So go ahead. Go ahead. I'm sorry. Go ahead. I thought great. Go ahead
Need to be you need to be hurt clearly to interrupt every single time every fucking time
I'm new, so I don't know what the hell's going on.
OK, that's OK.
OK, it's simple.
When you hear somebody talk, don't talk over them.
It's real simple.
It's true.
who you are, but first of all, I would have been able to talk if you didn't fucking interrupt me.
So don't, don't, don't do that. Don't do that. Don't do that. Don't do that.
Can you guys get ready to talk when I fucking ready? If you wouldn't have kept interrupting me,
I'd have been able to talk with them. So you can shut the all the way the fuck up.
Shut the fuck up! Read that card! Read that card where I tell you to talk to God damn much!
Read that for the fucking card! Read that goddamn card!
I've been trying to, you interrupted me at least seven times in the past three minutes.
One, I was going to ask somebody, I was going to pay somebody for a fucking read, and that was my first one.
The second one was I was going to do the, you know, clips and all that shit, but you, Mr. fucking square head,
can't find any of your cards, did you talk to God damn much?
Okay. Let's all take a breath. Let's all take a breath. And it's like, sometimes there's
a lot of people on the panel. It gets a little bit hectic sometimes. I know maybe it wasn't
Um, no, it's like a breath but unless like let's go we can go anytime we can have a talking stick
We can like you know, I can put people on well if they'd like to have the floor and stuff like that
I'll put them on on full screens. They can talk but
Yeah, we need a con show we need I can do my bell I can do a little thank you William Golding
The author of the Lord of the Flies, the country.
Oh yeah, and remember that book,
that's a great book guys.
Yeah, so let's, we can go one at a time
and I'll say who would like to have the floor.
We don't have to do it, it's like,
all of us can be mindful, you know what I mean?
Like we set up here with all kinds of people
and talk shit, you know, in the middle of arguing
a bit of a still understand each other.
It just seemed like every time I talk,
oh boy, the new dude is like boom, boom, boom.
These are you talking
It's okay
Fucking Jesus Christ
I don't know if you're doing it on purpose, but I mean seriously fucking finish
Like
Yeah, I just I just love you I ain't backing you just because you're my girl
You know you didn't get triggered you sat down let somebody speak over you a thousand times
And then you ain't gonna just let it happen over and over
He was wrong and you know what? I didn't like some up because now he's gone and we'll get over this psyche really quick
Is it if you're gonna talk just say you're sorry don't say I'm fucking new you were like yo listen dude
It's not about being new just fucking shut up right when I'm gonna
He's not new because his first thing on the first since it's on the show was I've been on 200 panels
So he knows what the I mean like, you know, I mean
Some of you I love you so much and anytime you raise your voice. It's because a motherfucker, you know, I mean don't stop
I love it when you're like
You're like other times past right the moments past
No, I understand if I prefer frustrating it, you know, but it's hard with you know people on panels
It's like, you know, there's a lot of people sometimes people have audio issues and things only I know he didn't
But you can't you can't be the first thing if you come up and I'll say you've been on 200 shows, you know
It's not for any purpose, but it's just anyway, let's get back to send the pop back to the cart
So you were explaining how the devil card can be
When somebody gets it, they shouldn't it ain't always a bad thing. You could be coming out of something bad, right?
Yes, yeah, especially if it's in reverse, I would say but also, you know, it's like it is also a capricorn energy
So maybe it's like you're in the capricorn in the capricorn energy
It's not always bad to be attached to the material world, you know
It's like but you know that it can lead to that, you know, like things like addictions
I can look in the I can read you exactly from the the
From the writer weight when it says about the devil car was always interesting to hear from the
There's very it's kind of short the descriptions in this but it says the devil it's a number 15
And so it's also corresponds to number six, which is the lovers and also compare the devil card to the lovers
The lovers it's kind of like adam and eve and this devil card is kind of like adam and eve fallen
Okay, so it says the devil it says ravage violence force
um behemoths extraordinary efforts
Fatality that which is um predestined but not for not this reason evil
it is reverse, evil, fatality, weakness, pettiness, and blindness. So this has like kind of a more
negative, it makes, like sometimes the people will translate the reverse in a more negative way,
but there's other ways to translate, it just depends on the energy if you're feeling about it,
because I think the reverse, some people say it makes it worse, but I'd say the reverse can kind
of mean also coming out of that, coming out of those things, and so it depends on how you want
because I was just going to ask you that coming out of reverse and you said it right before I was
going to ask you. So I'm starting to understand more because that's cool man.
I'll tell you what, Psyche's on this stuff.
I remember when Psyche used to come to talk to your aunt
and he would do readings for everybody
and like every single time,
I don't think I've ever heard one of their,
and you know, when you get to know people,
like I know some of you guys like that come to the show
and shit like that.
So I'd hear him doing their readings
and I'm like, man, he is right on it.
Yeah, that's what attracted me the most.
Psyche has a gift.
There's no doubt about that.
You're absolutely right.
Well said.
Because Miser said that to me the other night and I was kind of like scared to ask psyche because his channel is getting popular
And I'm like elementary and he put it the way you just said it
So two people could say almost the same exact thing with the way somebody says it is really important
You really do have a gift psyche. She hit the nail on the head buddy
Well, I was all about perspective though. Yeah
Each person's perspective, maybe that's why their readings might be a little bit different or something. I don't make them pick up different things.
Elliot, you're right. Totally right.
I love it.
I've been reading since I was, well I had my first deck, you know, since I was eight years old and I've always been interested and I bet it's like, you know, in the past several years I've gotten much more into it and like, you know...
Yeah, and really it's readings like you do that too. I do what do you do like 99?
I saw like one do I never heard of this until like you really like I know cards
But never heard like the term tarot so I went to this one page and I was just listening
I didn't say and they were doing like 99 cents readings. I was just curious if you do that
Do you do like 99 cents like?
you know whatever yeah well I was well I started out just doing like free readings and just like
you know it's like because I was just starting my channel and then I go to panels and do I do
free readings and things like that and it's like and now you know the the man and like there's more
people and that kind of stuff I like you know I do like you know I'll do more cards for five
dollars I'm doing I'm doing more longer readings for members and things like that and like tonight
Um, for $10 and it's like, you know, I'm gonna do my first one.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna throw you a super chat because I, yeah, I'm gonna, I'm gonna probably do one too.
I just want to say something real quick.
Michael said, if you say something wrong, I'm going to call you out.
No one said anything wrong.
That was the point.
You couldn't hear what I said.
So you were being emotional because you wouldn't shut the fuck up and you hear what I had to say.
So you're like, if I call you out.
Psyche didn't say anything wrong, school, the earth page, none of them said anything wrong.
So you just kept over talking you weren't listening at all it had nothing to do with you calling anything out
Why'd you run if you call it shut out because you run like a track star? So who you calling out what?
And the moments past we let it go
We was talking and you couldn't get your word, okay, then we let you get your word in you didn't say nothing
Yeah, you just came up here now to argue like we passed that you left for some reason no
we told you to leave removed on
I was about to pay him for a reading summer was and now you came back up here to talk about it again
Like let's just move on from it now. You don't have to leave everything. Let's move on. Is that cool Michael?
Some of we weren't even talking about it anymore, you know, you wrote it in the chat
Okay. All right. Cool. New day. New dollar. How you doing, sir?
No, I like Macy's face. I like Macy's face. How you doing, Summer? How you doing?
I like Macy's face. How you doing? Good. How you doing?
All right. We good. We good, Summer? All right, man.
Let's do it. I can admit I can apologize I can admit that
I'm gonna look for the super chat you got 99 cent
You do that you should like throw up readings like that like maybe someone yeah, yeah
Because you're really good at it and it's like what's 99? You know what I mean any way to donate or
Just think that was like a good idea that channel had the 99 cent reading
Yeah
Yeah, I'll definitely do I'll do
Yeah, I believe in that because this is an art form, you know like someone who's an artist
They're like, oh, would you like a signed picture with my you know signature? I'm like, no
I'd like to buy artwork from you, you know, and that's like
doing from you because
Somerset you really have a gift
Thank you
Yeah, I'm gonna use the money. I want to I want to read
Okay, you got it. I'm gonna send it to cash it like you do you um, oh, you'll monetize now psych, right? Yeah
You know, I found that I
I'll be getting my I kind of miscalculated a little bit. I'll be getting my first payout
Um, it says this YouTube sends it, you know, that's between the 21st and 27th or so
Thank you. Do they take taxes out? How does it work? YouTube takes 30% of
of memberships and of super chats and so yeah super chats and so but also I
think that they you promote the super chat set that's also YouTube's making
money from that too so they probably maybe will put you higher in the
algorithm you never know. Yeah YouTube chats ain't nothing man just catch
What? Cash app is better than, uh, wait, so do you put your cash? What would you like?
Cash app is, cash app is always better for our students, let's just say.
You can eat our money out.
Hell yeah, we want to do that right now, so.
It's actually, the cash app is, um, scroll it on the bottom of the screen, it's also
pinned, that my, uh, my name on cash app, okay? So I really do appreciate that.
I'm doing it right now. I see on the green, the green thing going across, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm doing it right now, buddy.
So with you. Yeah, I want you to what is it was it?
Psych awaken. Oh, that's easy. That's your name. Yeah
Thank you and
What's your name?
My name is psyche awakens or you my name is John though. I mean, but it's
What do you feel at summer what's up, I'm Michael hood
Hell yeah, all right. Yeah be coming over to you tonight because
We on the screen
No, thank you. I'm gonna be on the screen. It should come through tell me when you got it. Okay
That what part is that me sir?
Me is that your artwork that because I know you're you're me
I'm doing
Christ hard this little guy is gonna go on the bottom. Okay. That's beautiful. I keep went through and then he's gonna be
This is what's gonna be in the background
Nuclear waste, you know, we're gonna have a little halo around the guy
Pretty cool, I'm gonna put myself full screen for a second so I can do a halo
I like that there you go
Very cool. I'll do myself on full screen for a second so I can do school of Athens
This is my first one ever psych. I've never ever had a reading in my entire life like not at a carnival or
Like ever so I've never had any type of tarot reading to me ever
Well, it's interesting. I just I just like you know kind of split the deck and and I came up with these two these two queens energy
And so I don't know if these are these are women in your life
There's a queen of panicles the queen of cups and so this is a woman that's very very grounded and and
Bountiful and that everything grows around her and she's nurturing and then we have the queen of cups and very similar
She's a very controlled for emotion, but she but she's at the same time emotional
She feels emotions strongly. How many cups do I get?
I'll do a couple more because these just came out together. It just seemed like you have these two queens
And so I want to write it in so I can research them answers, you know pentacles would have put a P and
Queen of Cups, right? Yeah. Okay next. You know the queen of Panticles is on the she's on the earth, you know
She's very connected to the earth and you know
And then the queen of cups is on the ocean right and it's her the rippling waves and she has kind of her foot on the ocean too
Okay
Alright, okay, then we got it's a big one here. I'm feeling this is the this is the four of swords
And this means like getting some rest
Okay, well, I'm feeling that that card right there that means something
Mm-hmm research that shit the four of swords. Yeah, why is it? Why does it look like he's dead?
You know like a knight or like a case that's that's yeah
It does but it does resemble like a kind of a sarcophagus in a way
And that's done, but he's also at peace.
So I think this card is some rest also,
like there's another, there's a card,
I think it's the seven of swords where it's like,
he's sitting up, he's sitting up in like this,
not the seven of swords, I'm sorry,
it's probably the six of swords where he's sitting up
worried and stuff like that.
And like that can mean like you're sitting there,
you know, in like mental distress,
this is more of like, you're not worried, you're resting,
I'm having anxiety about things. Okay, here's some
Does a person ever pick the card from you like do you has it ever done that way or no?
I
Sometimes like I've had I've done reading for people that prefer like I'm doing a reading in person
Like I can sometimes spread it out and have them pick a few cards, you know
What's the seventh card right now from the top like to me like what's the seventh card?
That's my okay. Okay. One two
four
So we have the star card. This means I say make a wish. There's also like the love being poured from above
The name say on the bottom of that is the star. I'm sorry. I'll put it. It's just star. That's what it's called
It's called the star or anything like there's no suit
No, it's an it was called the major arcana. There's the minor cards, which are the
I think I have to cover her a little bit because she's nude and stuff like that to be careful
But yeah, there's like this bright star, you know, I'm shining over
It's also a special coin
Also associated I also associated with the with the Aquarius energy because you know
Aquarius is the water bear and she's kind of pouring and so as I associate it with a queer Aquarius and stuff like that
But she's uh, she's pouring into this rip and there's a ripple effect too
But I say always when I get this card I say make a wish because you make a wish on a star, right?
I just I feel like is that called like special or like if there's a card that like doesn't have any like
You know two clubs three clubs four clubs like the star it sounds like it's like in a class of its own
Is that yeah, so there's the there's a major arcana. It's called the major arcana
Which is like there's the 22 major cards and it's like and then the minor arcana is more
It can get more into certain details about things, but the major ones are major cards. And so it's like a big
ARC and a arcana, right?
Thank you psyche
You're welcome. And so I hope you like that reading
I appreciate everything wrong
Totally different from the conversation I had with me. Is there the other night I look at it completely different than I did
Yeah
I received your yeah, thank you so much. I'll do like a 13 cards for you. Okay
Yeah, so I had to be careful with some of the nudity on these cards, but there's a Sun card
This is like the most positive card of the deck and so maybe I think this is like your natural bright energy illuminating situations
There's but there's a lot of happiness here. There's like he's kind of has a little victory flag. He's on a horse
The horse is kind of an interesting look on his face. I'd be careful with the nudity
Notice the most positive card in the deck
Also the emperor, okay, so this is I'm not sure if this is a man of your life
But this is like all the kings in the deck, you know, and he's a he's ruler
He's also I would say this is like a lot of fire energy and so you mentioned that you are
Capricorn Aquarius cusp, which is like earth and air, but also there's a lot of fire in you
And you can you tell by you tell by your hair right because he's wearing red red is also associated with fire
But this guy he's like a master of the master of his unit
Okay, and you know, he's got there's a there's a Rams heads too
So, you know, there's a you might want to check your your placement if you what's on Aries air is also the first house
So you might want to check your first house placements. Okay, so this man in your life or okay
So please do not interrupt my reading, please. I'm begging. I didn't say where you know
But also we got this night on this night of wands because the night of night of wands, especially the first, you know
It's coming in in reverse and it's like, you know, that could be somebody coming in and you know
Like sometimes it's like, you know
People can rush in and they can like either like come in like light your fire or they can come in and set your house on fire
And stuff like that. I'm not I'm not talking, you know, and it's but the night of wands is known for rushing in and out
And especially this guy he might not be too trustworthy
You might want to watch out for this night of wands rushing in rushing out
Okay, also
You've also got this world in your hands. Okay control of your world and you're also you're waiting for something right there
He's waiting. It's probably sees a ship out in the water and he's like he's because he looks like he's kind of navigating
He's waiting for a ship to come in also
You're getting a lot of fire. There's a lot of fire in this reading. Okay, so far. Okay, but I say that your
Your ship's coming in and you're you're waiting for something. You also got control control control of your material world in a circumstance, okay?
Okay, and also this is a five of pentacles that it's in reverse, okay?
Five of pentacles is traditionally being left out feeling left out in the cold about something
This is kind of like it turns from like a window where they don't feel welcome
But it just kind of turned into a door where the door is open to you
Okay, so maybe if you've been feeling left out of something it that's going to be changing you know
You're gonna be feel welcomed in okay
Okay, what else do I got for you also coming together? There's two of cups
This is like, you know, this is like doing a cheers with somebody. This is kind of an equal partnership
It could be divinely ordained with the also, you know
That's like, you know, the the the fire energy to with that with that the the lion the winged lion up there
They're also mingling their energies. They're also it's they're also holding the cups up, you know
They're looking into to their eyes. It's kind of an equal partnership. Okay?
So
Hello?
Why are you doing rock? I'm doing something like... hold on, I don't know what it was.
Yeah, oh, hi guys!
I want to thank the person for, hold on, let me have a minute.
Okay, did you hear me?
There's my microphone on, hello.
Okay, we're live now, we're live, we're live, okay.
I just got your super chat.
Thank you so much for the super chat, by the way.
Okay.
reverse shows pentagram? Yeah. Yeah, I mean there's you know pentagram is
traditionally inside a circle and so a circle traditionally has no top or bottom
and so you know there's no there was like the inverted pentagrams kind of
like just you know in perspective of what pentagram really is right.
Traditionally they have the pentagram is five
By a pointed star it's a really easy pattern to draw that everybody knows how to draw. Hi guys
But it's also powerful magical symbol
It's showing you know all this all the elements are separate, but united and they all unites into the
You're the highest form of you know
You know a lot of life the live person with intelligence like or maybe whatever else it can create
but anyway
Some of these are old it'd be I feel like you know
It's pretty cool. I get to host my old shows
I think because it's like some of these old shows are it's not just like oh
It's like some boring show like covering something. It's like
There's like family the show is a mystery if you like watch the show, but even I don't know all the mysteries show
I'm still like am I covering?
Little interesting thing and plus I couldn't I was so drunk when I first started doing this
Oh, he's so drunk because it was just like that's a weird
Atmosphere, you know, I said oh party party party and so I just got used to drinking. I was almost every day
and
did to drunkenness
And I say I would even remember some of the things
It's so it's a weird life, and then I like kind of like
If you need like that through being drunk, oh my god, you have to do some structure on that side of my door right now, huh?
Anyway, you hear that? So anyway, um
But now I've gotten kind of sober my I don't know what kind of it's like, you know, I still drink a little bit and it's like
Not really, I'm wasting money on beer, but now I'm spending more other stuff and the uh,
I gotta stop.
I'm just gonna start getting like, just the dollar value menu or like, the
cheapest stuff at McDonald's off the app every day, I can't, but it's gonna be like the easiest, like, wait,
you still eat, or else I can just have like, you know, ramen diet, which is no fun.
I just get like, good stuff.
I don't really eat very much though.
let's see but what do you want to do let me see i have a i don't know oh yeah i was trying to
tell you like nothing my i don't even know if i can't use my like my mouse right now
can i oh every time you know my keyboard every time i try to type even on like the two keyboards
i put in there it's like now it's like um just like shutting everything down so i thought i'd
Hi Amanda, thank you for being here, thank you for the donation earlier too.
I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to do a lot of series, I'm going to do a special series.
Oh, hold on. Hello? Ah! Woohoo! Let's go, let's go baby!